Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/manishmishra-37753545 (LinkedIn) www.cssindia.in (Company) yahoo.com (Personal) www.cssindia.in (Company)

MANISH MISHRA

Call center at "Clear secured Services"Pvt. Ltd.sion(w) mumbai-400022

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Corporate generalist attorney with substantial in-house legal experience. High premium on providing preemptive legal support in French or English. Focus on intellectual property, contract drafting and union negotiation.

Financial exec with broad experience in all aspects of accounting, auditing and financial management. Direct experience with real estate, financial consulting and venture capital. Interested in early-stage startups as well as companies "on the bubble."

Application Developer, Database Administrator, and Project Manager in a wide variety of business applications. Particularly interested in client/server and relational database design using Oracle, Sybase, and MS-SQL Server. Always interested in migration projects, as well as close interaction with the DB manufacturers.

Licensed Psychotherapist focused on providing individual and couples counseling services. Specializing in work related stress, womens' issues and family mediation services. Interested in academic work as well, and perhaps advising corporations on mental health issues.

Specialties: Competitive analysis, financing, franchising, mergers and acquisition

Nonprofits, real estate law, tax planning, code compliance Film output, 4-color process, pre-press, storyboarding XML, HTML, JavaScript, usability, CSS, WYSIWYG layout tools

Experience

CSS PVT. LTD. MUMBAI- 400022 CALL CENTER at November 2011 - Present central railway near Sion(west) Hello I'm Manish mishra.I am coming from Allahabad is most popular city now i live in Mumbai city & I am doing job CSS pvt. ltd. Sion(west) Mumbai-400022.

Web add- www.cssindia.in.Contact no-7498444274,7498444272,7498444271.

Email ID- manishmishra8752@gmail.com.

Personal contact no.-8652787280,9930283980

"clear secured services" Pvt. Ltd. call center November 2011 - Present

Central railway sion(west) mumbai- 400022

Hello I am Manish mishra I am completed my software courses from "Keerti computer institute" & doing BCA from Tilak Maharashtra Vidyapeeth University Pune and i'm doing job "clear secured services" Pvt. Ltd. mumbai-400022.

Education

BCA at

Tilak Maharashtra Vidyapeeth university Pune, English · (2011 - 2012)

Tilak Maharashtra Vidyapeeth University Pune bachelor of comouter, English · (2011 - 2012)